http://www.jokesbar.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
A good laugh is sunshine in a house.
Search
You are here:
Jokes Menu
Animal JokesBlondes JokesChildren JokesComputers JokesDrunks / Bars JokesGender JokesLawyer JokesMedical JokesMisc. JokesPeople JokesPolitical JokesRelationships JokesReligious JokesSports JokesWork Place Jokes
Privacy Policy
Cookies We, and some of our partners who provide some of the services and products on our site, may use cookies to record session information, such as items that you add to your shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when you return to our site, and customize web page or email message content based on your browser type or other information. Log Files We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. WebTrends Live is used to analyze traffic to this web site. WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services WebTrends Live does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data. For more information about WebTrends Live privacy policy, please click here . Ad Servers and Other PartnersTo try and bring you offers and information that may be of interest to you, we may have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads or provide other services or products in our web site or e-mail newsletter(s). As a result of your visit to our site, these companies may collect non-personally-identifiable information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. In addition, we may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Legal Advice for You is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. Newsletter If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. The email list may be managed by a third party, such information as is necessary will be provided for such third party to manage the email list. In addition, the information and offers in the email list may result from consultations with third parties or may be created by third parties. The information in the list may also be syndicated and provided in conjunction with other web sites. Except as otherwise provided, this will not result in the release of any personal information except as necessary to provide for the delivery of the email list to subscribers. If you subscribed to our e-mail newsletter(s) but do not want to receive it in the future, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions contained in the newsletter(s).  In our email messages to you which are distributed through this list, we may have information from third party providers for products and services which may be advertised or promoted within messages we send to you from this email list. No individual information is provided to any third-party without your consent, but if you enter transactions with a third party as a result of an offer - through Template Site web site, email communication, or other means - those third-party provider sites govern the method by which they collect and use any information. Surveys & Contests From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.  Referral Service If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Template Site will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site.  Security of DataWe attempt to take reasonable measures to secure our data. However, we cannot guarantee that the measures taken are or will remain adequate. Since we may include links to other companies' web sites in the messages sent to the email list, please refer to the privacy policies of those sites for information on how they handle security for information they collect.   Site and Service Updates We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.  Correction/Updating Personal Information If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support. Changes to Privacy PolicyFrom time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Email List Privacy Policy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to this Email List Privacy Policy page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of our list. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at this Email List Privacy Policy page periodically.  Business Transfers As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy web sites or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if Template Site or substantially all of its assets are acquired or merged with another company, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.
Additional Information
Sayings
I believe in practicing prudence at least once every two or three years.Molly Ivins
Latest Funny Pictures
bigdog
Partner
Powered by Joomla!
